# **Andrew Krikorian**

#### **Software Engineer**

akrikorian12@gmail.com - (650)455-1223 1048 La Cuesta Rd, Hillsborough, CA 94010

# **Biography**

A passionate programmer who is currently double majoring in Comp Sci and Econ. Loves the process of gaining new experiences and learning as much as possible. Possesses more than 2 years of hands-on professional programming experience as well as 2 years of working on data analysis and business strategy teams.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Data Science Intern

#### Silicon Valley Bank

x June 2021 - August 2021 (Remote)

• Worked on the Mortgage Business Insights team analyzing and modeling current and future mortgage businesses. Used MongoDB to store and retrieve all data and Tableau to create all the mortgage dashboards.

### Full Stack Engineer Intern

#### **America's Best Beverages**

x June 2021 - August 2021 (Remote)

• Worked with the executive team to develop a new website for their Cloudburst Coffee branch. We used agile methodology which I curated and worked with Minion Made to rehaul their online presence altogether. We used ReactJs with some UI frameworks as well as Shopify's API.

#### Software Engineer Intern

#### **ESO Fund**

x June 2016 - Aug 2016 ( Foster City, CA)

x June 2017 - Aug 2017 (Foster City, CA)

• Worked on ESO's lead generation team. I helped develop a chrome scraping tool using JS. After developing the tool, I worked on creating different stable funnels of SQL by redeveloping our tool and scraping different sources using our scraping tool.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Edvisor.com (WIP)

#### **Founder**

- School Scheduling Automation Tool for high school graduates and transfer students.
- React, Tailwind, Chakra, JavaScript, Firebase



# Rebrand.ly/andykr1k

#### **Developer Portfolio**

- LinkTree Style Portfolio
- React, Tailwind

### **SKILLS**

- Languages Proficient: C++, JavaScript, Python, Swift/SwiftUI, HTML, TailwindCSS // Familiar: Assembly, C, C#, Solidity,
- Frameworks Proficient: React, Next.js, RedwoodJS // Familiar: Svelte, Angular
- Backends Proficient: Node.js // Familiar: Go, Python, Ruby
- Databases Proficient: Firebase, Supabase // Familiar: Redis, MySQL, PostgreSQL

#### **EDUCATION**

University of California Riverside - Computer Science and Economics Dual Degree

x Sep 2022 - Jun 2024

College of San Mateo - Computer Science and Economics Dual Degree

x Sep 2019 - Jun 2022

### **Profiles**

LinkedIn - linkedin.com/in/andrewkrikorian

Github - github.com/andykr1k

Portfolio - rebrand.ly/andykr1k

## References

SVB - (Head of Private Bus Insights) - Sukhuma Sukal -

sukhuma.sukal@gmail.com

ABB - (CEO/Founder) - Hovig Azadkhanian -

hovig@americasbestbeverage.com

ESO - (CEO/Founder) - Scott Chou - Scott@esofund.com